<GodGuardDefs><List>	
	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_1">
		<DisplayName>Leigong</DisplayName>
		<Rate>12</Rate>
		<Names>fluorescent</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_lei</Icon>
		<Desc>The protection method that controls the power of thunder, enshrinement can comprehensively increase various abilities, and additionally increase the skill level of magic weapon, magic power, but it will reduce the magic aura's recovery speed.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_1</Modifier>
	</Def>	
	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_2">
		<DisplayName>Electric mother</DisplayName>
		<Rate>12</Rate>
		<Names>River</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_dian</Icon>
		<Desc>The protection method that controls the power of lightning, enshrinement can comprehensively increase various abilities, and additionally increase the skill level of the magic weapon. The magic aura's recovery speed, but it will reduce the magic power.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_2</Modifier>
	</Def>	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_3">
		<DisplayName>Yun Ting Shen Jiang</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>flash</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_yun</Icon>
		<Desc>The method of protection that controls the power of the cloud and wind, enshrinement can slightly increase various abilities and increase the skill level of the body, but it will reduce the magic power.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_3</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_4">
		<DisplayName>Thunder Lord</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>shock</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_yu01</Icon>
		<Desc>The protection method that controls the power of rain and thunder, enshrinement can slightly increase various abilities and increase the skill level of the body protection, but it will reduce the magic aura's recovery speed.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_4</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_5">
		<DisplayName>Missing</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>palace</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_lie</Icon>
		<Desc>One of the five envoys of the Mine Ministry, enshrinement can increase the maximum life and aura, and increase the magic power, magic aura, and magic aura recovery speed.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_5</Modifier>
	</Def>	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_6">
		<DisplayName>Thunderbolt</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>mine</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_pi</Icon>
		<Desc>One of the five minions of the mine, enshrining can increase the maximum life and aura, and increase the magic power, but it will reduce the shield strength.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_6</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_7">
		<DisplayName>Divine Angel</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>mysterious</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_shen</Icon>
		<Desc>One of the five minions of the Thunder Ministry, enshrinement can increase the maximum life and aura, and increase the magic power, magic power, and magic cost.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_7</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	

	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_8">
		<DisplayName>Make heaven</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>set</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_tian</Icon>
		<Desc>One of the five minions of the mine, enshrinement can increase the maximum life and aura, and increase the skill level of the weapon, the skill level of the spell, and the skill level of the body.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_8</Modifier>
	</Def>	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_LeiBu_9">
		<DisplayName>Yushu</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>universe</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_yu</Icon>
		<Desc>One of the five minions of the Mine Ministry, enshrinement can greatly increase the life span and maximum aura.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_LeiBu_9</Modifier>
	</Def>	
		
		
	<Def Name="Guard_BaBuZhong_1">
		<DisplayName>Heavenly</DisplayName>
		<Rate>12</Rate>
		<Names>emperor</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>The first of the eight tribes, enshrinement can greatly improve all abilities, and learn the supernatural power: the view of the mind.</Desc>
		<Modifier>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_tian</Modifier>
		<Magic>God_Xiuwei1</Magic>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_BaBuZhong_2">
		<DisplayName>Dragon King</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Long</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_long</Icon>
		<Desc>Among the eight lords who control the ocean beings, enshrining can increase all abilities in small amounts, and acquire the skill: Royal Dragon Roar, and additionally increase the skill level and power of the spell, but it will double the cost of the spell.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_BaBuZhong_2</Modifier>
		<FightSkill>FightSkill_God_Damage1</FightSkill>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_BaBuZhong_3">
		<DisplayName>Yaksha</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Luo</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_ye</Icon>
		<Desc>Among the eight tribes, the king of agility and covert protection, enshrined can increase various abilities in a small amount, and acquires the mana: Yasha blood curse, and additionally increases the mana power, mana consumption, reduces mana chanting time, and adjusts his breath. time.</Desc>
		<Modifier>FightSkill_God_FightSkill1</Modifier>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_BaBuZhong_4">
		<DisplayName>Gandapo</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>fantasy</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_qian</Icon>
		<Desc>Among the eight tribes, the protection of the change of 缥缈, enshrining can increase various abilities in a small amount, and additionally increase the speed of magic aura recovery and reduce the consumption of magic aura.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_BaBuZhong_4</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_BaBuZhong_5">
		<DisplayName>Ashura</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>magic</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_a</Icon>
		<Desc>Among the eight members, it represents the law of killing evil thoughts. The enchantment can improve various abilities a little, and learn the spells: Xiuluo sword, and additionally increase the combat skill level, the weapon skill level, the spell skill level, and the body protection skill level.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_BaBuZhong_5</Modifier>
		<FightSkill>FightSkill_God_FaBao1</FightSkill>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_BaBuZhong_6">
		<DisplayName>Galuro</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Peng</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jia</Icon>
		<Desc>Among the eight ministries, it represents the divine protection of the majestic power. The enchantment can slightly improve various abilities, and additionally increase the flying speed, magic weapon speed, and magic weapon turning speed of the royal weapon.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_BaBuZhong_6</Modifier>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_BaBuZhong_7">
		<DisplayName>Kinaro</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>fun</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jin</Icon>
		<Desc>Among the eight groups, it represents a protector of beauty and tranquility. Enshrinement can improve various abilities a little, and learn spells: tranquility, and additionally increase charm, lifespan, and maximum aura.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_BaBuZhong_7</Modifier>
		<FightSkill>FightSkill_God_Health2</FightSkill>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_BaBuZhong_8">
		<DisplayName>Moroga</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Rob</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_mo</Icon>
		<Desc>Among the eight constituencies, representing the king of all living beings on the earth, enshrinement can improve various abilities by a small amount, and additionally increase the shield skill level and shield strength.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_BaBuZhong_8</Modifier>
	</Def>	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_YouMing_1">
		<DisplayName>Tongyou Magistrate</DisplayName>
		<Rate>12</Rate>
		<Names>Lee</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_tong</Icon>
		<Desc>The Netherworld governs the law of life and death, enshrinement improves all abilities, and gains magical powers: reversal of yin and yang, additionally increases the level of defense skills, and the maximum aura.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_YouMing_1</Modifier>
		<Magic>God_ResurrectionB</Magic>
	</Def>	
	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_YouMing_2">
		<DisplayName>Impermanence</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Fan</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_hei</Icon>
		<Desc>Ghost world ghost, enchantment can increase all abilities by a small amount, learn spells: impermanence protection, and additionally increase the skill level of magic weapon, magic power, magic aura, magic aura recovery speed.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_YouMing_2</Modifier>
		<FightSkill>FightSkill_God_Sheild1</FightSkill>
	</Def>	
	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_YouMing_3">
		<DisplayName>White robe impermanence</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>thank</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_bai</Icon>
		<Desc>The ghost world ghost ghost, enchantment can increase all abilities by a small amount, and additionally increase the spell skill level, spell power, spell consumption.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_YouMing_3</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_YouMing_4">
		<DisplayName>Ngau Tau Envoy</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Cattle</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_niu</Icon>
		<Desc>Netherworld inspectors, enshrined can increase all abilities by a small amount, and additionally increase the shield strength and magic power.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_YouMing_4</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_YouMing_5">
		<DisplayName>Horse face ghost</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>horse</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_ma</Icon>
		<Desc>Netherworld inspectors, enshrined can improve all abilities by a small amount, and additionally increase the strength of shield and spell power.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_YouMing_5</Modifier>
	</Def>	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_YouMing_6">
		<DisplayName>Extradition</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Meng</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_yien</Icon>
		<Desc>In the ghost world, the Styx extradites people, enshrining can increase the lifespan and the maximum value of the aura, and also obtain magical powers: soul rejuvenation, extra magic power, magic power.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_YouMing_6</Modifier>	
		<Magic>God_ResurrectionA</Magic>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_YouMing_7">
		<DisplayName>Yinshanwei</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>what</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_yin</Icon>
		<Desc>Underworld guardian of Netherworld, enshrine can increase the life span and the maximum value of Aura, and increase the shield strength.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_YouMing_7</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_1">
		<DisplayName>Greedy Star</DisplayName>
		<Rate>12</Rate>
		<Names>kill</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_tan</Icon>
		<Desc>The spirit of the stars is very fierce, and enshrinement will increase all abilities, and additionally increase the power of magic weapons and spell power, but it will greatly reduce the life.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_1</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_2">
		<DisplayName>Seven Stars</DisplayName>
		<Rate>12</Rate>
		<Names>kill</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_qi</Icon>
		<Desc>The spirit of the stars is very fierce, and enshrinement will increase all abilities, and additionally increase the magic power and spell power, but will greatly reduce the upper limit of the aura.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_2</Modifier>
		<FightSkill>FightSkill_God_Damage2</FightSkill>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_3">
		<DisplayName>Breaking star</DisplayName>
		<Rate>12</Rate>
		<Names>military</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_po</Icon>
		<Desc>The spirit of the stars is very fierce, and enshrinement will increase all abilities, and additionally increase the power of magic weapons and spell power, but will greatly reduce the strength of the shield.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_3</Modifier>	
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_4">
		<DisplayName>Chi Ling</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>red</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_chi</Icon>
		<Desc>The ancient five-party five-element protection method, enshrinement will increase all abilities by a small amount, and additionally increase the spell skill level and spell power.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_4</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_5">
		<DisplayName>Bai Ling</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>White</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_bai</Icon>
		<Desc>The ancient five-party five-element method of protection, enchantment will increase all abilities by a small amount, and additionally increase the magic skill level, magic power, magic aura upper limit, magic aura recovery speed.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_5</Modifier>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_6">
		<DisplayName>Huang Ling</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Ji</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_huang</Icon>
		<Desc>The ancient five-party five-element protection method, enshrinement will slightly improve all abilities, and additionally increase the body protection skill level and shield strength.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_6</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_7">
		<DisplayName>Black Spirit</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>juice</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_hei</Icon>
		<Desc>The ancient five-party five-element protection method, enshrinement will improve all abilities by a small amount, and additionally increase the sense of gas.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_7</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_8">
		<DisplayName>Qingling</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>spirit</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_qing</Icon>
		<Desc>The ancient five-party five-element protection method, the enchantment will slightly increase all abilities, and additionally increase the maximum aura.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_8</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_9">
		<DisplayName>Hailing</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Wang</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_hai</Icon>
		<Desc>I do n’t know what kind of shinto protector came from. Enshrinement will increase all abilities by a small amount, and also increase the magic power.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_9</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_10">
		<DisplayName>Mountain Spirit</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Thai</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_shan</Icon>
		<Desc>Enshrining the spirit of mountain protection law will increase all abilities by a small amount and increase the shield strength.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_10</Modifier>
		
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_11">
		<DisplayName>Flower spirit</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>Fragrant</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_hua</Icon>
		<Desc>Hundred Flower Guardian Spirit, enshrine will increase all abilities by a small amount, learn spells: Ten Thousand Flower Curse, and increase the maximum aura maximum.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_11</Modifier>	
		<FightSkill>FightSkill_God_Health1</FightSkill>
	</Def>	
		
	<Def Name="Guard_Other_12">
		<DisplayName>Giant spirit</DisplayName>
		<Rate>9</Rate>
		<Names>worship</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_ju</Icon>
		<Desc>Enormous law-enforcement, enchantment will increase all abilities by a small amount, and additionally increase the ability of the magic weapon to repel, and the magic weapon's ability to resist repel.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Other_12</Modifier>
	</Def>	
	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_1">
		<DisplayName>Jin Jing</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>blade</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the magic skill level, magic power, magic aura upper limit, and magic aura recovery speed.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_1</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_2">
		<DisplayName>Wood spirit</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>leaf</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the maximum Reiki.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_2</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_3">
		<DisplayName>Water essence</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>flow</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this method of protection can improve the sense of gas.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_3</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_4">
		<DisplayName>Fire spirit</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Yan</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the spell skill level and spell power.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_4</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_5">
		<DisplayName>Native spirit</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>dust</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protection method can increase the body protection skill level and shield strength.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_5</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_6">
		<DisplayName>Tusha</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Ginseng</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_sha</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase lifespan.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_6</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_7">
		<DisplayName>Musha</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>spirit</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_sha</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the maximum aura value.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_7</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_8">
		<DisplayName>Jinsha</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Extinguish</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_sha</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this law can increase the power of magic weapons.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_8</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_9">
		<DisplayName>Hu Jing</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>to</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the recovery speed of magic aura.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_9</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_10">
		<DisplayName>Jing Jing</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>明</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the magic aura.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_10</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_11">
		<DisplayName>Yan Jing</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>thick</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protection method can increase the strength of the shield.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_11</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_12">
		<DisplayName>Fire</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Fiery</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_sha</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase spell damage.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_12</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_13">
		<DisplayName>Water</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Decide</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_sha</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can reduce spell cost.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_13</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_14">
		<DisplayName>Feng Jing</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Howl</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_jing</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the flying speed of magic spells.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_14</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_15">
		<DisplayName>风煞</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>鸣</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_sha</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this law can increase the turning speed of magic weapons.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_15</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_16">
		<DisplayName>Yansha</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Hold</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_sha</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the magic weapon's knockback distance.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_16</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_17">
		<DisplayName>Tenacity</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>Firm</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_sha</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protection method can increase the resistance of the magic weapon to repel.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_17</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_18">
		<DisplayName>Mu Gang</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>leaf</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_gang</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can reduce spell chant time.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_18</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_19">
		<DisplayName>Shuigang</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>wave</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_gang</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can reduce the spell's breath adjustment time.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_19</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_20">
		<DisplayName>Jin Gang</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>copper</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_gang</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the skill level of the weapon.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_20</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_21">
		<DisplayName>Huogang</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>flame</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_gang</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protector can increase the spell skill level.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_21</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_22">
		<DisplayName>Tugang</DisplayName>
		<Rate>6</Rate>
		<Names>pulse</Names>
		<Icon>res/Sprs/ui/icon_shenguo_gang</Icon>
		<Desc>There is no main protection law everywhere between heaven and earth. Enshrining this protection method can improve the body protection skill level.</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_22</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<!-- 
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_23">
		<DisplayName>水精</DisplayName>
		<Names>流</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高根骨。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_23</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_24">
		<DisplayName>火精</DisplayName>
		<Names>焱</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高神识。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_24</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_25">
		<DisplayName>土精</DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高魅力。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_25</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_26">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高悟性。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_26</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_27">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高机缘。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_27</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_28">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高法宝威力，法术威力。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_28</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_29">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高法宝灵气恢复速度，降低法术消耗。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_29</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_30">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高法宝威力，护体效果。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_30</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_31">
		<DisplayName>金精</DisplayName>
		<Names>刃</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高术法威力，护体效果。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_31</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_32">
		<DisplayName>木精</DisplayName>
		<Names>叶</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高御器技能等级，护体技能等级。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_32</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_33">
		<DisplayName>水精</DisplayName>
		<Names>流</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高术法技能等级，护体技能等级。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_33</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_34">
		<DisplayName>火精</DisplayName>
		<Names>焱</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高御器技能等级，术法技能等级，护体技能等级。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_34</Modifier>
	</Def>
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_35">
		<DisplayName>土精</DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高灵气最大值，法宝威力。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_35</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_36">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高灵气最大值，术法威力。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_36</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_37">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高灵气最大值，护盾强度。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_37</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_38">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高寿命，灵气最大值。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_38</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_39">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高寿命，法宝威力。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_39</Modifier>
	</Def>
	
	<Def Name="Guard_Base_40">
		<DisplayName></DisplayName>
		<Names>尘</Names>
		<Icon>Res/Sprs/ui/xrui_bg39</Icon>
		<Desc>天地间随处可见无主护法。供奉此护法可以提高寿命，术法威力。</Desc>
		<Modifier>Modifier_Guard_Base_40</Modifier>
	</Def> -->
</List></GodGuardDefs>