<Helps><List>
	
	<Help Name="999">
		<Title>Sky Covering World</Title>
		<Text>
		[CDATA[
		[color=#FF4040]Dare to ask God if there is a fairy[/color]
		[Zhu Tian World] is a mod created by the author [Destruction of the Door] based on [Chen Dong] 's famous novel "Zhu Tian". It aims to restore the grand world of "Covering the Sky".
		[color=#238E23]Special reincarnation[/color]:Ye Fan, who suppresses all the enemies in the world, has his back to the lifeless Emperor, Ji Ziyue, and there are dozens of powerful heaven-covering samsaras.
		[color=#238E23]Special exercises[/color]:The non-learnable scriptures without congenital Eucharist, the unbelievable magical power of the ruthless emperor, Devouring Magical Powers, and the Tao of Covering the World ’s spiritual practice, add up to ten powerful imperial scriptures. Practice
		[color=#238E23]Special plot[/color]:Follow Ye Fan's footsteps, from the coffin in Kowloon to the legendary Nine Secrets, and go all the way to the invincible heaven. The rich plot rewards and powerful plot enemies make your road to immortality no longer boring.
		[color=#238E23]Special items[/color]:The ancient tree of Wudao, which is recurring for thousands of years, has hidden sources of strange and strange sources, which can create physical fluids that are comparable to the sacred constitution, eat yaochi peaches that can prolong life, and cover a lot of items in Tianyuan's original works.
		[color=#238E23]Special Treasure[/color]:Destroying the ancient gods' list of gods, deterring the world's no-start bell, Xuanhuangqi created all kinds of mother spirit, and the powerful emperors in the sky reappeared in the world
		[color=#238E23]Special Skills[/color]:Is it just boring to accumulate numerical values? Chaos effects, minus the aura cap, silence enemies, increase condemnation, a variety of special effects to meet your diverse tastes
		[color=#238E23]Elixir system[/color]:It is no longer possible to plant only the five-element elixir. The five kinds of elixir of the green dragon, white tiger, suzaku, basalt and yellow dragon in the sky can also be planted. In addition to harvesting a large number of five-element elixir each time, you can also obtain some special herbs with a small probability.
		[color=#238E23]Holy City Treasure Breeder[/color]:By consuming life, you can buy most of the items in the game, and at the same time you can show your skills in the gambling stone workshop.
		[color=#238E23]Source stone system[/color]: The path to the development of the Eucharist, but people are the protagonists. For everyone, in your world of cultivating immortals, destroying the door still covers the sky with your hands, depending on your face.
		[color=#238E23]Holy City Gambling Stone[/color]: A concept similar to Yuan Shi, but with a different gameplay (all in the sky font size) has now been added with black point, rock-paper-scissors. Two ways to play. Small gambling is good, big gambling hurts. Taoist, do you bet?
		[color=#238E23]Title system[/color]: You can get different titles in the holy city through the options of moving the world. There is also a chance to unlock a special title "My Child King Teng the Great", and at the same time continuously collect various secondary 2 and cool titles in the group.
		The above is the completed content of this mod, which will be continuously improved in the future. Interested friends can add groups
		[color=#FF00FF]Skyblock mod mods[/color]: 602303528 (a group) 
		[color=#FF00FF]Skyblocking World Mod Two Groups[/color]: 780991793 (two groups)
		
		[Covering the sky] MOD exclusive activities:
		1. Nonstop title collection. Dissatisfied with the title of Jie Danhou, or feel that the title does not match his invincible villain, then cover the sky group. Demon Sermon Satisfies Your Soul of Secondary Two
		2. Intermittent weapon customization activities. Choose the weapon you want based on the weapon map provided by the author. And name it. The selected weapon will be placed in the Shenfangfang for all players.
		3. The design of major holy places and the end time of the event are tentative. During the period, I hope to receive a large number of works covering the sky. Make a contribution to the improvement of the heavenly world.
		]]>
		</Text>
	</Help>
	<Help Name="1111" Root="999">
		<Title>Reward sponsorship</Title>
		<Text>
		[CDATA[
		[color=#FF7F00]Reward the QR code:[/color]
		MOD has been around for half a year so far, thank you all for your company and support.
In the future, the cover world will also be made better, so that cover fans can feel the cover world, and those who have not entered the pit can like cover sky.
A word of reward! If everyone likes my work ~ just love and give a reward ~. But it ’s good to be there, even I ’m happy. Because with your approval. Thanks guys, finally
		Happy New Year!
		[color=#007FFF]WeChat reward code ————[/color]    [img]Spr\Object\WX.png[/img]
		
		[color=#007FFF]Alipay payment code ————[/color]    [img]Spr\Object\ZFB.png[/img]
		
		]]>
		</Text>
	</Help>
</List></Helps>